<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prerequisites on Modern Infrastructure as Code with Pulumi</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prerequisites on Modern Infrastructure as Code with Pulumi</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Start the Workshop...</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites/start_workshop.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites/start_workshop.html</guid>
      <description>Getting Started To start the workshop, follow one of the following depending on whether you are&amp;hellip;&#xA;&amp;hellip;running the workshop on your own, or &amp;hellip;attending an AWS hosted event Once you have completed with either setup, continue with Install the required tools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a workspace</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites/workspace.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites/workspace.html</guid>
      <description>The Cloud9 workspace should be built by an IAM user with Administrator privileges, not the root account user. Please ensure you are logged in as an IAM user, not the root account user.&#xA;This workshop was designed to run in the Oregon (us-west-2) region. Please don&amp;rsquo;t run in any other region. Future versions of this workshop will expand region availability, and this message will be removed.&#xA;Ad blockers, javascript disablers, and tracking blockers should be disabled for the cloud9 domain, or connecting to the workspace might be impacted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create an IAM role for your workspace</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites/iamrole.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites/iamrole.html</guid>
      <description>Starting from here, when you see command to be entered such as below, you will enter these commands into Cloud9 IDE. You can use the Copy to clipboard feature (right hand upper corner) to simply copy and paste into Cloud9. In order to paste, you can use Ctrl + V for Windows or Command + V for Mac.&#xA;Follow this deep link to create an IAM role with Administrator access.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attach the IAM role to your Workspace</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites/workspaceiam.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites/workspaceiam.html</guid>
      <description> Follow this deep link to find your Cloud9 EC2 instance Select the instance, then choose Actions / Instance Settings / Attach/Replace IAM Role Choose Pulumi-Workshop-Admin from the IAM Role drop down, and select Apply </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update IAM settings for your Workspace</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites/10_cloud.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites/10_cloud.html</guid>
      <description>Cloud9 normally manages IAM credentials dynamically. This isn&amp;rsquo;t currently compatible with the some AWS services authentication, so we will disable it and rely on the IAM role instead.&#xA;Return to your workspace and click the gear icon (in top right corner), or click to open a new tab and choose &amp;ldquo;Open Preferences&amp;rdquo; Select AWS SETTINGS Turn off AWS managed temporary credentials Close the Preferences tab Let&amp;rsquo;s run the command below, the following actions will take place as we do that:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resize workspace&#39;s EBS volume</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites/volume_resize.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites/volume_resize.html</guid>
      <description>The Cloud9 workspace volume should be resized by an IAM user with Administrator privileges, not the root account user. Please ensure you are logged in as an IAM user, not the root account user.&#xA;This workshop was designed to run in the Oregon (us-west-2) region. Please don&amp;rsquo;t run in any other region. Future versions of this workshop will expand region availability, and this message will be removed.&#xA;Set up resize script: Create a file called resize.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Pulumi &amp; Language Dependencies</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites/50_workshop_setup.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/10_prerequisites/50_workshop_setup.html</guid>
      <description>These hands-on labs will walk you through various cloud infrastructure tasks. The prerequisites listed below are required to successfully complete them.&#xA;Pulumi In order to run this workshop you will need to work with the Pulumi CLI.&#xA;You will use Pulumi to deploy infrastructure changes using code.&#xA;To install Pulumi run the following command:&#xA;curl -fsSL https://get.pulumi.com | sh source ~/.bashrc Now restart your Cloud 9 terminal&#xA;After installing the CLI, verify that it is working:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
